testbanker.com 2007-12-02

# Privacy Plicy

|   
  
---  
  
|  |  |  |   
---|---|---  
|   
**Collection and use of personal information**  
---  
TestBanker attempts to limit required information at registration to only that which is required to validate a unique user. Most of the required, personal information we collect is very basic, such as name, email address, and password. Thereafter, it is at the user’s discretion to provide optional information on the site’s pages. Aside from the personal information you explicitly provide to us, we collect browser info, IP address, and other such details from all users of TestBanker. Furthermore, we store certain information regarding each user and browser utilizing cookies and other technologies to enhance the personalized experience and keep track of user traffic. We do not use said technologies (i.e. “cookies”) to obtain any personal information.   
  
**Navigation information**  
Even if you are not a registered user of our site, we have the ability to track usage and traffic on our site (including the server, browser, and location from which the site was visited). This information is never used to track or obtain personal information from users, but is used on an aggregate basis to customize our site, plan advertising, and improve the overall online experience.   
  
**Information voluntarily provided**  
There are times when you may provide voluntary information (feedback, suggestions, emails, letters, posts, uploads, forum comments, etc.). Any such information can, and may, be utilized by TestBanker in any way it finds appropriate to improve customer service, track website usage and data, and/or improve the site or services offered in any way.   
  
**Sharing and protection of your information with others**  
TestBanker will share your personal information only with staff members who need it to do their job on the site. TestBanker does everything possible to protect your information and will not intentionally release private information to other users without your explicit consent. TestBanker can, and may, share your information with third parties if: (1) TestBanker needs to do so to enable service providers to help bring services to our users or our site. (2)TestBanker needs to do so to facilitate business practices, such as email solicitations. (3) TestBanker is required by law to do so (subpoenas, court orders, laws, etc... (4) TestBanker must share info to comply with laws and/or to protect TestBanker’s or its users’ interests. (5) TestBanker would undergo a change of ownership (all info would be transferred to the new owners). We do not sell or rent customer lists to third parties. Occasionally, we may provide information to companies who work with us to help provide services.   
  
**Those under the age of 18**  
TestBanker recommends that minors over the age of 13 get a parent or legal guardian’s permission before registering on our site or sending any information about themselves over the internet.   
  
**Children under the age of 13**  
TestBanker does not consciously collect information from anyone under the age of 13 or allow such users to register. If you are under the age of 13, please do not attempt to register on our site or send any information regarding yourself to TestBanker. In the event TestBanker has learned it has collected information from any person under the age of 13, we shall delete the information or account as soon as possible. If you believe we have collected such information or a child under the age of 13 has registered on our site, please let us know at TestBanker@gmail.com.   
  
**Links to other sites**  
TestBanker contains many links to other sites. When a user leaves TestBanker.com, the user is responsible for understanding the privacy practices of the other site. TestBanker is not responsible for any other sites’ privacy practices or the displaying of their policies. This privacy policy deals solely with TestBanker.com.   
  
**Advertising**  
Some advertisements which appear on our site’s pages are third party advertisements. These third parties may download cookies to your computer. Doing so enables advertisers to track which computers are seeing their advertisements and where they are located. In this way, advertisers can target their audience in attempts to deliver the most relevant ads to you, the user. TestBanker does not have access to nor control over third party cookies that may be downloaded to your computer.   
  
**Changes to the privacy policy**  
TestBanker reserves the right to make any changes and/or modifications to its privacy policy. Any such changes will be posted on this page with the effective date being changed to the date of the posted modifications. TestBanker encourages all of its users to regularly check back for alterations in the Privacy Policy to keep current with its policies.   
  
**Contacting TestBanker**  
If you have any further questions and/or comments regarding the privacy policy or TestBanker, please visit our contact page for more info.  
|  |
